{
    "subject": "resource/A._Carl_Helmholz",
    "predicate": "ontology/field",
    "object": "resource/Nuclear_physics",
    "human_readable": "A. Carl Helmholz's field of study is Nuclear physics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.928260862827301,
            "question": "How has Carl Helmholz's work contributed to the field of nuclear physics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8784944415092468,
            "question": "Was Carl Helmholz a physicist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7931692600250244,
            "question": "What field of study did Carl Helmholz specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7091166377067566,
            "question": "What area of physics did Carl Helmholz focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6419233679771423,
            "question": "Who are some other notable figures in the field of nuclear physics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3665658235549927,
            "question": "Can you give an example of research conducted in nuclear physics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36151063442230225,
            "question": "What are some key concepts within nuclear physics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3046271800994873,
            "question": "How has nuclear physics impacted our understanding of the universe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22868722677230835,
            "question": "What are the potential applications of nuclear physics in everyday life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20887793600559235,
            "question": "What are some ethical considerations related to nuclear physics research?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=A. Carl Helmholz's field of study is Nuclear physics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3005_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the potential applications of nuclear physics in everyday life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3005_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has nuclear physics impacted our understanding of the universe?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3005_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key concepts within nuclear physics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3005_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3005_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3005_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3005_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3005_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3005_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3005_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3005_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3005_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3005_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3005_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"A. Carl Helmholz's field of study is Nuclear physics.\" Several documents mention his involvement in nuclear physics, including his work with Ernest O. Lawrence on the cyclotron, his participation in the Manhattan Project, and his long career at the University of California, Berkeley, where he was a professor of physics focusing on nuclear studies."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}